Jaydatt Champavat

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ENGINEER · FULLSTACK DEVELOPER 141/2, Sector-28, Gandhinagar 382028, Gujarat, India

Summary_

Currently a freelance web developer. 2+ years of experience specializing in web development and infrastructure automation utilizing industry forefront tools such as **ExpressJS**, **Node**, **MongoDB**, **ReactJS**, **GraphQL**, **GatsbyJS**, etc. Adept in React workflows with several state management libraries (**Redux**, **XState**, **Recoil**, etc). Interested in delivering better and creative methods of problem-solving for challenging tasks, and keen to explore and learn new technologies and tools.

Skills

Languages and Databases TypeScript/Javascript/ES6 Java Python PHP CSS/SASS/SCSS MongoDB MySQL

Frameworks and Libraries (NodeJS (ExpressJS)) .NET (GraphQL) ReactJS (VueJS) Redux & XState (GatsbyJS) (GraphQL)

Tools and Workflows GIT AWS Docker Webpack/Parcel Jest redis

Work Experience_

Slick Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

Remote - Ahmedabad, Gujara

Jul. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN
- Created stable and maintainable codebases with performant and accessible React components.
- Creating features, functionalities and extending capabilities of a ERP Single Page Application built in React, MaterialUI, Redux and Redux Saga.
- Worked briefly on Shopify eCommerce using Liquid, JQuery and JSON.

Samaj Infotech Gandhinagar, Gujara

JR. NODEJS DEVELOPER

Jun. 2019 - Nov. 2019

• Implemented a RESTful API server and an ERP Single Page Application for a management system consisting of product manufacturing management, Inventory management, Accounting, User Authorisation and Invoice generation in MERN stack.

Honors & Achievements

2019 **Collaborator**, GatsbyJS

2018 **27th Rank**, CodeChef API Hackacthon 2018

Ahmedabad, Indi

Ahmedabad, India

Projects

2018

bDownload

GITHUB REPO

- A batch downloader cli made in NodeJS.
- Download using HTTP or curl, Output folder selection, Batch downloading

Regionals Qualifiers, Gujarat Industrial Hackathon 2018

rhythmix

GITHUB REPO - DEMO

- A polyrhythm trainer and tester for musicians made in ReactJS.
- · Listen to and practice to different polyrhythms or custom polyrhythms.

Education

Silver Oak University

Ahmedabad, India

2017 - 2021

• 7.85 CGPA (till 6th semester)

Kendriya Vidyalaya No. 1

Gandhinagar, India

2017

12TH GRADE/HIGH SCHOOL

. 86%